One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
The Mysterious Visitor!
The Two Warlords Meet!
W-What a scary woman.
We told her...
Everything.
But Perona-sama also loves treasure.
That's right!
She won't be able to take it from her!
Treasure Room of Mast Mansion
Then again, we told her about the shortcut.
She got us.
How conceited!
Not only is she stealing our treasure...
But she also plans to take the Sunny and escape?!
I'm not letting that happen!
Moreover, what's with this bridge?
Why is this the only thin part?
Although it's strangely well made.
I've had enough of you!
I will crush you all!
I didn't see anything!
You better get ready!
I'm gonna squash you all!
No bone will be left unbroken!
He's extremely angry now!
Not good! Not good!
Here he comes.
I can't move!
My horns are...!
Damn it!
My horns got stuck in the ground!
It's over...
You can't move, huh?
That sounds like Oars' screams.
But... that's impossible!
Cut it out already!
Withdraw!
Right!
What cruel guys.
So flipping him over doesn't work.
Look!
A mountain of meat!
What?!
Knee Crusher!
Making him kneel counts as a down?
Even if there were any rules, I don't think he'd play by them.
They did it! Totally kneeling!
Alright! Totally kneeling!
How humiliating.
We won't lose to you!
We'll just have to hold you until Straw Hat defeats Moriah!
Hurry and retrieve the shadows, Straw Hat!
Why do we have to wait?
Let's beat him ourselves.
H-H-Hey! We're just holding off this monster so he doesn't go after Straw Hat!
Don't tell me you wanna beat this thing?!
First there's no meat...
Then they take me down to my knees.
Once you start a battle, you have to end it!
He's an insanely huge zombie!
There's no choice but to purify him!
He's right, Zoro!
Let's just buy some time!
If you don't like it, you're free to run.
I'm not gonna wait for Luffy either.
Rubber...
Even if a dinosaur were to step on it, it wouldn't bend a millimeter.
I heard this black sword's greatest trait is its hardness.
This Great Grade Sword I just obtained, Shuusui...
Shuusui: Clear Autumn Water
This is the perfect chance to test its power!
Wait!
Luffy's gonna beat Moriah for us!
Wait a minute, you!
Who is that?
It's the pirate woman.
What're you planning to do with the treasure I was planning to steal?!
And with the Sunny?!
I thought it was someone else, but it's just the pirate woman.
Is your wedding with Absalom over already?
Like I'd marry that perverted, invisible beast man!
So you escaped after all.
What a useless man.
So... what will you do?
It's true that I plan to take your ship to leave the island.
If you want to prevent that, you'll have defeat me.
For a weakling like you, this amount of mini hollows will be enough to tear you apart.
That nega-nose is my only natural enemy.
Who's that?
Perona-sama, run away!
Who the hell are you?!
We don't know who he is, but he's an enemy!
Just now, our brothers were erased right before our eyes!
He's no pushover!
He's dangerous!
Of course he...
is not a pushover...
He is...
One of the Royal Warlords of the Sea,
The Tyrant, Bartholomew Kuma.
A man who committed every brutality a pirate can.
No way! A Royal Warlord of the Sea?!
Impossible!
A man equal to Moriah-sama?!
Why's he on Thriller Bark?!
No way.
Are you Moriah's subordinate?
M-Moriah-sama-
No!
Gekko Moriah has nothing to do with me anymore!
I-I was about to... leave this island!
If you were to go on a trip, where would you like to go?
He wants to chat?!
Why do you want to hear-
But if I went on vacation, I'd stay in a dark, damp, and evil old castle...
Spending my days singing cursed songs.
She answered!
As expected from the Ghost Princess!
I got carried away!
How dare you make fun of me!
I was overwhelmed by your reputation for a moment.
But I have no reason to fear.
There's no human I can't make kneel with my ability.
Are you listening?!
Your shadow must be really powerful, Kuma!
I will defeat you and give Moriah-sama your shadow as a farewell gift!
Negative Ghost...
Plus...!
Special Hollow!
Here it comes!
Perona-sama's ultimate combo!
Judging by your actions...
I assume you aren't going to tell me Moriah's whereabouts.
Where'd she...?
Where did you go, Perona-sama?!
Perona-sama!
Hey, what's going on?!
Perona-sama vanished!
Bastard, what have you done to our princess?!
This is unforgivable!
We won't forgive you!
He's too scary!
Run!
The Burglar Cat, right?
One of Straw Hat's crewmates.
Is it true that Monkey D. Luffy...
has a brother?
What?
He got here in an instant!
Did he warp?
It is!
You mean Ace, right?
What about him?!
I see. So it was true.
What do you mean?
Did you come for Luffy?
What're you after?!
Are you really a Warlord?!
Whatever I do... is my problem.
He's dangerous.
Is he after Luffy?
I must tell everyone.
I got you, Moriah!
You're not going anywhere, you bastard!
Now fight me!
And give everyone's shadows back!
A shadow?
Dawn.
The Shadow Recovery Time Limit Approaches
D-Damn it!
He tricked me!
You!
Wait!
Moriah's shadow!
Don't leave me here!
Where am I?!
Hey!
Damn it, this is bad!
I promised everyone I'd get all the shadows back.
I'm in serious trouble without mine.
Let's see...
What was gonna happen to me without my shadow?
That's right!
If we stay like this, we'll dissolve in the sun's light!
This is bad. I gotta hurry before the night's over.
Now, come.
I will be your opponent!
Fine.
The difference in weight is clear between this black sword, Shuusui, and its predecessor Yubashiri.
Yubashiri: Snow Run
Hey Zoro, watch out!
With this weight...!
Incredible!
He deflected that punch!
Three Swords Style...
108 Pound Cannon!
It's huge!
Shuusui's strike absorbed the slashes of the other two swords to join into one!
But... it seems there's too much pointless destruction in the blade.
Proof that I've yet to master it.
Its destructive power is way bigger, but...
This is no easy sword to control, it seems.
You've given me something good,
Swordmaster Ryuuma.
You're not bad.
Had I taken that, I'd be history.
You bastard!
I'll crush you all!
Hey!
Don't attack so recklessly.
Even if you manage to defeat him, only Luffy's shadow will be released.
We don't even know where your and Sanji's shadows are!
But... if Luffy beats Moriah, we'll get all the shadows at once.
There's no point in hurting yourself fighting that huge zombie!
For now, just have faith in Luffy and keep this monster at bay!
I have plenty of faith in him.
Luffy also has his weakness, you know...
His gullibility.
An invisible man...
A ghost woman...
A ruler of shadows.
This island is infested with people who have such abilities.
Don't expect that they'll fight Luffy fair and square.
That is true.
Yeah.
If he fools Luffy and morning comes...
Neither he, nor I, nor the cook...
None of us three will be able to fight anymore.
But... if we can at least make Luffy go back to normal before daybreak...
He might still do something!
I don't think we even have thirty minutes before daybreak.
The fog is extremely thick in this sea.
It must be restricting the reach of the morning light by now.
So it's almost morning.
We're only alive because of this fog.
Whether it's morning or not, I'm finally starting to feel the danger of the situation.
W-What?
What's this shaking?!
What's this?!
Just like before, the ship is stuck in another weird sea current!
Hey, look at the sky!
I can see the predawn sky!
The fog has started to clear!
What's going on?!
Could it be... that we're already out of the Florian Triangle?!
It's Oars' fault for messing with the rudder before!
That bastard and his dumb games!
Moriah-sama!
Big trouble!
The Thriller Bark ship has come out of this foggy sea!
It's all Oars' fault!
Moriah-sama!
Leave it that way.
What's the big deal anyways?
We're pirates!
We sail up and down the seas as we please!
E-Even so...
More importantly; we have a most unusual visitor today, so be silent.
Isn't that right?
The Tyrant, Kuma.
The only man among the Warlords of the Sea that is truly loyal to the government!
You're very important to the government, but...
I've no idea what someone as uncanny as you could be scheming.
If you were to travel, where'd you go?
Hey, hey, stop it.
I'm fully aware of your abilities.
Have you come here to pick a fight?
Speak your business.
Why have you come here?
I have a certain matter to report.
The replacement for the Royal Warlord of the Sea, Crocodile.
His successor has been chosen.
You should've said that in the first place.
Who is he and what sea is he from?
There are countless pirates.
The name of the successor is...
Marshall D. Teach,
A man commonly known as Blackbeard.
Blackbeard?
Never heard of him.
He's a fugitive from Whitebeard's crew.
He caused quite an uproar around the world recently.
The news have yet to reach the sea of the mist.
He earned the title through merit.
So, what's his former bounty?
Zero.
I see.
An unassigned quantity.
It's impressive that the government acknowledged him.
Well, they must be at ease now that they've filled the gap.
Then I guess this means the world is keeping its balance, right?
No.
I think quite the opposite.
But that matters not.
More importantly, the government has a bigger concern right now.
Since the events at Enies Lobby... the actions of the Straw Hat pirates are being watched very thoroughly.
It was most likely that they'd be delayed here traveling from Water 7 to Fishman Island.
So... have you realized what the government's current concern is?
That yet another...
Warlord of the Sea will fall at the hands of the Straw Hat pirates.
That's what the government fears.
Don't mess around!
They're worried about me?!
Just because someone else got stripped of their title by some puny pirates...
they think the same will happen to me?!
If you can't take care of them yourself, I'm willing to help you.
Who do you think you're talking to, bastard?!
Do you actually think I'd lose to that insignificant and amateurish crew?!
In battle, nothing is 100% sure.
Back at Enies Lobby, who would have imagined that Rob Lucci could be defeated?
That's exactly my point!
Is the government so scared that they're sending two Warlords of the Sea to eliminate them?!
Huh!?
I'm only here to report.
I did not receive such orders.
Then, just shut up and watch!
And also, give this message to that pack of know-nothings!
"The Straw Hat Pirates you're so scared of have easily been...
turned into loyal soldiers of Gekko Moriah's zombie army!"
The fog...
This is terrible.
That thick fog was our only ray of hope.
Who would have plotted for the fog to clear out at a moment like this?!
At this rate, we'll get burnt by the morning light straight on!
An unexpectedly refreshing night sky.
I-It's Moriah...!
It's Moriah!
Huh?
It's nearly daybreak.
Do you really have time to fool around?
Why're you here?
What happened to Luffy?!
Hey, what're you talking about, Usopp?
Where's Moriah?!
Are you blind?!
He's over there!
His belly...!
He's inside Oars' belly!
Inside his belly?!
H-He is!
Then, where's Luffy?
Was he tricked after all?
Or maybe...
Luffy won't fall that easily!
Found him! He's in a cockpit?
What, there was a cockpit in my belly all along?
This is really cool!
I'm somewhat like a robot!
Now, I will give you a chance to fight me.
If you defeat me, you can release all the shadows!
You can come at me all together!
But be aware that unless you defeat Oars, you can't reach me!
That bastard!
That's dirty!
We can't purify Oars unless we defeat Moriah.
But, Moriah is inside Oars now.
We've got a clearer target now, it seems.
Let's do it!
Usopp.
Since little portions don't work, go find a large quantity of salt and bring it!
That's the only way to purify Oars.
We'll do as much as we can to weaken him!
Alright, I got it!
I'll get it!
I'm sure there was a kitchen in the mansion!
There must be a large supply of salt in there.
Salt, huh?
Hey, Oars.
Eliminate that long-nose heading for the mansion.
Don't let him reach the kitchen alive.
Yes, Master.
Damn it!
Usopp!
No good.
Now that Moriah is here, he's acting like a brain for Oars.
Usopp!
Where are you?!
Answer me!
He's safe!
I thought you'd need a large quantity of salt.
So I brought plenty of it!
Brook!